

BENJAMIN OHENE KONADU

JUNIOR FULL – STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



KONRAD-ADENAUER-STR 253 52223 STOLBERG GERMANY +4915216646714 +4917684256361 benohenekonadu@yahoo.com

LINKS

GitHub: LinkedIn:

https://github.com/Benohene https://www.linkedin.com/in/benjamin-ohene-konadu/

PROFILE

Junior Software Developer with a Diploma in Full-Stack Software Development from Code Institute. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Python. I have about 6 years of experience in Graphic Design. I create many designs both static and motion. I am a valuable team player with strong communication skills and effective problem-solving ability. I am eager to gain entry into the tech industry into an exciting development team where I can grow and contribute!

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA

Code Institute (Accredited by the University of West of Scotland) 12/2022 - 08/2023

Diploma in Full-Stack Software Development (E-Commerce)

BACHELOR OF ART

Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology - Ghana 09/2009 - 06/2013

BA Integrated Rural Art and Industry (Specialised Textiles & Product Design)

WASSCE CERTIFICATE

Anglican Secondary School - Ghana 10/2005 - 06/2008 Visual Arts

SKILLS

Technologies: HTML 5, CSS, JavaScript, Python **Frameworks:** Bootstrap, jQuery, Flasks, Django

Database: MySQL, PostgreSQL

Version Control: Git, GitHub

Others: SEO, Web Marketing, Stripe with Django, Agile Methodologies, Software Testing and

ΔPIS

Graphic Design: Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator Corel Draw, Rhinoceros 3D, WordPress, Flyers, Logos,

Poster, Video & Photo Editing

Other Skills: Microsoft Office Suite

PORTFOLIO PROJECTS

Youth Aflame Social Club

Git Hub: https://github.com/Benohene/youth-aflame-sc-project.git

Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, UX Design, GitHub Pages

YA Bible Quiz Game

GitHub: https://github.com/Benohene/ya-bible-guiz-project.git

Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, UX Design, JS ES6, Browser Interactivity.

Benny Graphyx Interview Terminal

GitHub: https://github.com/Benohene/benny-graphyx-inteview-pp3.git

Technologies Used: Python 3, Heroku, Automation

Full stack Toolkit - RANDY BARBERSHOP

GitHub: https://github.com/Benohene/PP4-Randy-Barber.git

Technologies Used: Agile, Bootstrap, jQuery, Software Testing, APIs, Databases, Django

E-Commerce Applications - PB MAJESTIC CLODING

GitHub: https://github.com/Benohene/pb majestic cloding.git
Technologies Used: Web Marketing, SEO, Stripe with Django

WORK EXPERIENCE

Media-Head - Gospelhaus International Chapel – Aachen

Feb 2019 - Present

- Media setups
- Graphic Designs and Website Manager

Freelancer (Graphic Designer) - Self-Employed

Aug 2017 - Present

- Create digital and printed designs like posters, flyers, banners and many more
- Use Adobe Creative Suite to create images and layouts.
- Design website layouts, templates and unique brand looks.
- Create videos for social media, advertising and informational purposes.

Warehouse (Junghaus Wolle Versand GmbH - Aachen, Germany)

Sep 2019 - Apr 2022

- Picking and Sorting
- Dispatch/Sending

Relocation - Jul 2017-Aug 2017

Store Manager- ROB Enterprise (Family Business) - Kumasi

Feb 2015 - Jul 2017

- Successfully coordinated in-store events
- Resolved customer complaints promptly
- Promoted excellent communication within the team

Teaching Assistant (Department of Integrated Rural Art & Industry)

Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology - Kumasi

Aug 2013 - Jun 2014

- Help the lecturer with test management, curriculum creation, and grading.
- Record classroom activities and attendance.
- Supports the Lecturer in supervising a group of approximately 100 students.

INTEREST/ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Hackathon BY Code Institute - July 2023

Team Code wave Surfers - 2nd place

GitHub: https://github.com/Benohene/lovin summer.git

Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, UX Design, JS, ES6, Browser Interactivity, API

Currently studying Bootstrap Studio

LANGUAGES

English (Native) German (B1 Certificate) Twi (Native)

06.12.2023